<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BLOG — Index</title><link>(null)</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 15:19:36 -0400</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 15:19:36 -0400</lastBuildDate><item><title>Blog Post 1</title><link>(null)</link><description><![CDATA[<h1>Make People Feel Good With These Super Easy Gestures</h1><p>The next time anyone says something you like, whether friend, neighbor, family member, whatever…. you’ll make that person feel good if you do any one of the following:</p>
<p>    •    Give a thumbs-up.</p>
<p>    •    Clap your hands once.</p>
<p>    •    Drop your jaw.</p>
<p>    •    Tap your heart.</p>
<p>    •    High five, or fist bump.</p>
<p>    •    Point at them! And you can build in more emphasis:</p>
<p>    ◦    Point and wink.</p>
<p>    ◦    Point, wink, and click your tongue.</p>
<p>    ◦    Point, wink, click your tongue, and shake your hips once!</p>
<p>Can you see how you can build upon a simple move? Don’t be afraid to try this in the mirror. Of course you can make changes to adjust to your style! I’m giving specifics because some people like a jumping off point. Be playful with your body language.  It’s all good, as long as you makejust a little effort. The only mistake you can make is to be “above it all”, and not try something a little fun.</p>
<p>“We don’t stop playing when we get old. We get old when we stop playing.” — George Bernard Shaw</p>
<p>When you first see someone you know, and want to make them feel good:</p>
<p>    •    Say his/her name with great enthusiasm in your voice.</p>
<p>    •    You can add extra energy by drawing his/her name out:Jeffffrrrrrreeeeeeeee!! Hannnnaaaahhhhh!!</p>
<p>    •    Bend your knees, lean back, and clap your hands!</p>
<p>    •    Bend your knees, open your arms wide, and hold still a moment. Prepare yourself. You might get a hug this way!</p>
<p>You see people do this, and maybe you do it sometimes.  But few people put energy into getting better at it or doing it more often.  That’s a shame!  Gestures like thisserve many good purposes. They make someone else feel good for a moment. They also warm up your expressive face and body. We’re all expressive on the inside. The trouble is, as we grow up, some of us becomemore focused on words over actions.  And in the digital world, we socialize even more with words, and less with our natural gifts in primal talk. So, when you put in just a bit of effort, you’ll stand out. Make primal talk a habit and you’ll light up the room!</p><p>Menu</p><p><b>Home</b></p><p><b>About</b></p><p><b>BLOG</b></p><p><b>BLOG — Index</b></p><p><b>Blog Post 1</b></p><p><b>Blog Post</b></p>]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>(null)</guid></item><item><title>Blog Post</title><link>(null)</link><description><![CDATA[<h1>Feel Ready For Anything When You Strike This Pose</h1><p>Try throwing your arms over your head.  Almost everyone has done this.  This time, allow yourself to hold it a little longer than usual. </p>
<p>Circus performers do this bow at the end of their routine, the culmination of years of hard work.  This bow plays to the farthest seat in the arena.  Primates hit this posture when they want to assert themselves.  Victorious athletes do this. Even athletes who were born blind, and never seen throw their arms up, assume this posture when ecstatic.That’s how innate this pose is.</p>
<p>I’ve encouraged many folks to do this, because I know it makes me feel capable.  It makes you feel strong. I know for a fact that audiences around the world understand this.</p>
<p>I”m simply opening up here, and lifting my chest.    </p>
<p>As I do this , testosterone goes up. This makes me ready for a challenge, and boosts my confidence</p>
<p>And don’t think for a minute that testosterone is only a male hormone.  Women have it, too.</p>
<p>And male or female, you may be interested to know that your  Cortisol  levels goes down.  “The stress hormone”.</p>
<p>Try this pose in private for  minute, before you start your work day, andnotice how you feel. Can you see how your body language talks to yourself, not just others ?!</p><p>Menu</p><p><b>Home</b></p><p><b>About</b></p><p><b>BLOG</b></p><p><b>BLOG — Index</b></p><p><b>Blog Post 1</b></p><p><b>Blog Post</b></p>]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>(null)</guid></item></channel></rss>